<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Samoa Embassy</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/SE_Github_Site/index.php/feed/?simply_static_page=4902" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy</link>
	<description>Beijing</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 02:34:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[8th September 2017, Sheraton Aggie Grey’s Hotel, Apia-Samoa Pacific Leaders gathered in Samoa in September to attend the annual Pacific Islands Forum. The Agenda for this year’s meeting included the Small Islands &#160;Developing States Leaders Meeting, the Pacific ACP Leaders Meeting, the Official Opening of the 48th Pacific Islands Forum, the Forum Leaders Dialogue with &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>8th September 2017, Sheraton Aggie Grey’s Hotel, Apia-Samoa</p>



<p>Pacific Leaders gathered in Samoa in September to attend the annual Pacific Islands Forum. The Agenda for this year’s meeting included the Small Islands &nbsp;Developing States Leaders Meeting, the Pacific ACP Leaders Meeting, the Official Opening of the 48th Pacific Islands Forum, the Forum Leaders Dialogue with Civil Society Organizations and Private Sector, the 48th PIF Plenary Sessions with Associate Member and Forum Observers and Post Forum Dialogue Partners and the Forum Leaders Retreat.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Also during the meeting week, The Pacific Islands Trade and Investment Commission in China, the Samoa Embassy in China and its Chinese partners hosted a Seminar for business leaders, Officials and others interested in building economic links between China and the Pacific. The aim of the Seminar was to learn about the opportunities and challenges through participation in industry-focused panel discussions on trade, investment and tourism.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The opening statement for the Seminar was delivered by Samoa’s Minister of Commerce, Industry and Labour, Hon. Lautafi Selafi Purcell. Presentations on related topics were delivered by H.E Mr Du Qiwen China’s Special Envoy for the China Pacific Islands Forum Dialogue, Mr. Shiu Raj Director Policy &amp; Economic Governance, Pacific Islands Forum Secretariat, Mr. Yin Zonghua Vice President China Council for the Promotion of International Trade (CCPIT), and Mr. Guo Wanda Executive Vice President China Development Institute (CDI).</p>



<p>The one day event was attended by members of Samoa’s private sector, Government Officials, Pacific delegates and delegates from China. The Seminar focused on three main areas for panel discussions;</p>



<p>1.Chinese Partnerships in Pacific Infrastructure and Connectivity</p>



<p>2.Sustainable Tourism Development</p>



<p>3.Value-adding to Pacific Fisheries</p>



<p>The Seminar proved to be a great opportunity for the exchange of ideas and discussion of opportunities to further strengthen trade, investment and tourism between China and the Pacific.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="javascript:;"><img decoding="async" src="http://www.samoaembassy.cn/UploadFiles/2017-10/2/2017102401.jpg" alt="The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development"/></a></figure>



<p>Opening Statement: Hon. Lautafi Selafi Purcell, Minister of Commerce, Industry and Labour, Samoa.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="javascript:;"><img decoding="async" src="http://www.samoaembassy.cn/UploadFiles/2017-10/2/2017102402.jpg" alt="The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development"/></a></figure>



<p>China and the Pacific Islands: H.E Mr Du Qiwen, China’s Special Envoy for the China Pacific Islands Forum Dialogue.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China International Travel Mart, 11-13 November 2016</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/06/china-international-travel-mart-11-13-november-2016/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The CITM (China International Travel Mart) is well known as the largest International Travel Mart in Asia which has attracted audiences from across the globe.&#160; The annual event is alternated between Shanghai and Kunming with this years’ event being held in Shanghai. The CITM is an event jointly hosted by the China National Tourism Administration, &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/06/china-international-travel-mart-11-13-november-2016/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">China International Travel Mart, 11-13 November 2016</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The CITM (China International Travel Mart) is well known as the largest International Travel Mart in Asia which has attracted audiences from across the globe.&nbsp; The annual event is alternated between Shanghai and Kunming with this years’ event being held in Shanghai.<br><br>The CITM is an event jointly hosted by the China National Tourism Administration, the Civil Aviation Administration of China, and the Shanghai Municipals People’s Government.<br>The event was launched with the Official Opening Ceremony lead by the CNTA Chairman Mr. Li Jinzao with this year’s guest of honor Minister of Tourism and Sports for Thailand, H.E Kobkarn Wattanavrangkul.</p>



<p>Samoa’s delegation to the CITM 2016 included the Minister for Tourism, Hon. Sala Fata Pinati and his good lady Mrs. Cecilia Pinati, the Ambassador of Samoa to China, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, the CEO of the Samoa Tourism Authority, Mrs. Papalii Sonja Hunter, Marketing Manager, Mr. Dwayne Bentley, and First Secretary Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.</p>



<p>Other Pacific Islands that were also present at this years’ event included, Fiji, FSM, Tahiti, PNG, and Vanuatu.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="573" height="341" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news3.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1738" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news3.jpg 573w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news3-300x179.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 573px) 100vw, 573px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Lunch Meeting hosted by the Vice Chairman of the China National Tourism Authority, Mr. Du Jiang.</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="571" height="428" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news4.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1739" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news4.jpg 571w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news4-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 571px) 100vw, 571px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">The Hon. Minister for Tourism, Sala Fata Pinati, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, CEO of STA Papalii Sonja Hunter and First Secretary, Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="575" height="430" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news5.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1740" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news5.jpg 575w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news5-300x224.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 575px) 100vw, 575px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Pacific Delegates at the Expo Arena</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="573" height="429" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news6.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1741" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news6.jpg 573w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news6-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 573px) 100vw, 573px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Pacific Delegates at the Opening Cocktail</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guangzhou Tourism Expo, 9-11 September 2016</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/05/guangzhou-tourism-expo-9-11-september-2016/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1630</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Samoa in association with PITI attended the Guangzhou International Tourism Fair this year along aside other Pacific Island Countries such as PNG and FSM. The 3 day event was held at the well known Canton Fair Complex from the 9th- 11th September 2016. The Expo housed nine theme pavilions and 4,500 standard booths. Present at &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/05/guangzhou-tourism-expo-9-11-september-2016/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Guangzhou Tourism Expo, 9-11 September 2016</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Samoa in association with PITI attended the Guangzhou International Tourism Fair this year along aside other Pacific Island Countries such as PNG and FSM.</p>



<p>The 3 day event was held at the well known Canton Fair Complex from the 9th- 11th September 2016. The Expo housed nine theme pavilions and 4,500 standard booths. Present at this years Fair were 55 countries and more than 3,000 exhibitors. Also present during this years’ Fair were some special guests which included five Parliamentarians from Samoa, Hon. Tofa Foleni Loi, Hon. Salausa Dr. John Ah Ching, Hon. Leaana Ronnie Posini, Hon. Afoa Amituanai Mauli, and Hon. Fuimaono Teo. Further, The Governor and Vice Governor of Guangdong Province also visited the Pacific Booth and had brief discussions with Ambassador Tapusalaia on Tourism cooperation between China and Samoa.</p>



<p>The event also featured a tourism exhibition, a tourism hypermarket, a hospitality supplies fair, seminars, conferences, competitions, signing ceremonies and other events.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="571" height="424" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news7.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1742" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news7.jpg 571w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news7-300x223.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 571px) 100vw, 571px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Ambassador Tapusalaia meets with Governor of Guangdong Province, Mr. Zhu Xiaodan.</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="426" height="570" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1736" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news1.jpg 426w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news1-224x300.jpg 224w" sizes="(max-width: 426px) 100vw, 426px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="573" height="533" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news2.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1737" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news2.jpg 573w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news2-300x279.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 573px) 100vw, 573px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Samoa Embassy with Parliamentarians from Samoa.</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First World Conference on Tourism for Development</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/04/first-world-conference-on-tourism-for-development/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 08:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1759</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[18-21 May 2016 The First World Conference on Tourism for Development was held in Beijing from the 18-21 May 2016. Samoa’s delegation to the meeting was led by the Minister for Tourism Hon. Selafi Joseph Purcell with a delegation comprising of the Ambassador of Samoa to China, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, the CEO of Samoa &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/04/first-world-conference-on-tourism-for-development/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">First World Conference on Tourism for Development</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>18-21 May 2016</p>



<p>The First World Conference on Tourism for Development was held in Beijing from the 18-21 May 2016. Samoa’s delegation to the meeting was led by the Minister for Tourism Hon. Selafi Joseph Purcell with a delegation comprising of the Ambassador of Samoa to China, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, the CEO of Samoa Tourism Authority (STA) Ms. Papalii Sonja Hunter, Counselor of the Embassy of Samoa Ms. Helen Chou-Lee Tanuvasa and the First Secretary, Ms. Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.<br>The event was jointly organized by the Government of China and the World Tourism Organization (UNWTO) to encourage deliberations and create a better understanding of tourism’s contribution to development including poverty alleviation and peace. Further, China as the Chair of G20 also hosted the 7th G20 Tourism Minister’s Meeting during the event. Several heads of states as well as tourism ministers and senior officials from over 100 countries participated.</p>



<p>The UN has declared 2017 as the International Year of Sustainable Tourism for Development and a unique opportunity to portray tourism’s potential to help transform the world into a place of prosperity and wellbeing for all mankind. The conference highlighted the fast growing socio-economic benefits resulting from tourism and how tourism can stimulate economic growth, create employment opportunities and help small communities out of poverty.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="389" height="290" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news16.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1750" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news16.jpg 389w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news16-300x224.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 389px) 100vw, 389px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: From the left, Hon. Minister for Tourism of Tonga, Hon. Minister for Tourism of Samoa, Chairman of the China National Tourism Administration, Hon. Minister for Tourism of PNG, Hon Deputy Prime Minister and Minister for Tourism of Vanuatu)</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="388" height="288" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news17.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1751" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news17.jpg 388w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news17-300x223.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 388px) 100vw, 388px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: Chairman of the China National Tourism Administration, Mr Li Jinzao together with the Minister for Tourism of Samoa Hon. Lautafi Joseph Purcell)</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="207" height="275" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news19.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1752"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: Minister for Tourism of Samoa Hon. Lautafi Joseph Purcell and CEO of the Samoa Tourism Authority, Mrs. Papalii Sonja Hunter together with a performer from Guizhou Province)</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="355" height="267" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news20.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1760" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news20.jpg 355w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news20-300x226.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 355px) 100vw, 355px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: Minister for Tourism of Samoa Hon. Lautafi Joseph Purcell with the Ambassador of Samoa in Beijing, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata)</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 17th China International Vegetable Sci-Tech Fair</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 08:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1762</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[19th-21st April 2016 The Embassy of Samoa was invited to participate in this year’s China International Vegetable Fair which was held in Shouguang City, Shandong Province. The China International Vegetable Fair is the largest and most popular industrial exhibition meeting in China for the agriculture sector. The theme for this year’s event was ‘Green science &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The 17th China International Vegetable Sci-Tech Fair</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>19th-21st April 2016</em></p>



<p>The Embassy of Samoa was invited to participate in this year’s China International Vegetable Fair which was held in Shouguang City, Shandong Province.</p>



<p>The China International Vegetable Fair is the largest and most popular industrial exhibition meeting in China for the agriculture sector. The theme for this year’s event was ‘Green science technology and future under the principle of science, feature, innovation and practice for international agricultural exchange’.</p>



<p>The opening ceremony was attended by government officials, diplomats and hundreds of local farmers and members of the local business community. The ceremony was followed by an exhibition fair which occupied 450 thousand square meters of land including 11 exhibition halls, a foreign products exhibition pavilion, a vegetable museum, a vegetable picking park, numerous outdoor booths and 12 branches of exhibition company locations. Shouguang City is well known as China’s ‘Home of Vegetables’ and this year’s conference highlighted and showcased the extensive growth in produce and innovation of the agriculture sector in China.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="321" height="236" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news14.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1748" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news14.jpg 321w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news14-300x221.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 321px) 100vw, 321px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>(Photo: Far Right, Ambassador of Samoa H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata at the Opening Ceremony)</em></figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="171" height="230" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news15.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1749"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>(Photo: Tomato: One of the most popular fruits displayed at the Fair)</em></figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Outbound Travel and Tourism Market (COTTM)</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/02/china-outbound-travel-and-tourism-market-cottm/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/02/china-outbound-travel-and-tourism-market-cottm/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 08:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[12-14 April 2016 The Embassy of Samoa with the assistance of SPTO (South Pacific Tourism Organization) participated in the COTTM which was held in Beijing from the 12-14 April 2016. Over 400 exhibitors from 65 countries were present at the China Agricultural Centre to showcase and meet with tour operators, travel agencies, corporate buyers and &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/02/china-outbound-travel-and-tourism-market-cottm/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">China Outbound Travel and Tourism Market (COTTM)</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>12-14 April 2016</em></p>



<p>The Embassy of Samoa with the assistance of SPTO (South Pacific Tourism Organization) participated in the COTTM which was held in Beijing from the 12-14 April 2016. Over 400 exhibitors from 65 countries were present at the China Agricultural Centre to showcase and meet with tour operators, travel agencies, corporate buyers and business travel agencies to source new and exciting destinations as well as strengthen current relations.</p>



<p>The exhibition was an initiative to promote Samoa and the Pacific as an exciting tourist destination for the Chinese market. Other Pacific Islands that were also present in this year’s COTTM were Cook Islands, Vanuatu, Tahiti and PNG. China’s outbound market has been growing exponentially from 10 million in 2000 to projected 151 million in 2016.</p>



<p>At the conclusion of the 2 day exhibition, Samoa’s booth received 70 company representatives from the trade sector, 17 from the media and 14 others. Overall, the event was a great opportunity to engage with local and overseas service providers to help promote Samoa as an attractive destination for Chinese outbound travelers.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="267" height="177" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news9.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1744"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="214" height="321" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news8.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1743" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news8.jpg 214w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news8-200x300.jpg 200w" sizes="(max-width: 214px) 100vw, 214px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: (1) SPTO booth at the COTTM (2) Ambassador of Samoa H.E. Tapusalaia Terry Toomata and First Secretary of the Embassy of Samoa, Beijing)</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/02/china-outbound-travel-and-tourism-market-cottm/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fourth Session of China’s 12th National People’s Congress (NPC)</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/01/fourth-session-of-chinas-12th-national-peoples-congress-npc/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/01/fourth-session-of-chinas-12th-national-peoples-congress-npc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1766</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[5th March 2016 The &#8220;Report on the Work of the Government&#8221; was delivered by Premier Li Keqiang at the Fourth Session of the 12th National People&#8217;s Congress on 5th March 2016. Premier Li affirmed that although China faced some challenges such as downward pressure on the economy and frequent occurrence of natural disasters, China still &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/01/fourth-session-of-chinas-12th-national-peoples-congress-npc/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Fourth Session of China’s 12th National People’s Congress (NPC)</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>5th March 2016</em></p>



<p>The &#8220;Report on the Work of the Government&#8221; was delivered by Premier Li Keqiang at the Fourth Session of the 12th National People&#8217;s Congress on 5th March 2016. Premier Li affirmed that although China faced some challenges such as downward pressure on the economy and frequent occurrence of natural disasters, China still managed to overcome its difficulties under the leadership of the Central Committee of the Communist Party of China. (CPC)</p>



<p>The 13th Five Year Plan which was also delivered on the day outlines the Chinese Government’s policy frameworks and its priorities and economic and social development goals for 2016-2020. China’s new five year plan notes a series of key goals for the period 2016-2020 which includes the following.</p>



<ol>
<li>Double the 2010 GDP and per capita personal income</li>



<li>Annual spending: 2.5% of GDP</li>



<li>R&amp;D Spending: 2.5% of GDP</li>



<li>Science and Technology’s contribution to economic growth: 60%</li>



<li>Permanent urban residents: 60% of the total population.</li>



<li>Registered permanent urban residents: 45% of the total population</li>



<li>High-speed railways in services: 30,000 km, linking 80% of big cities</li>



<li>Expressways built or upgraded: 30,000 km</li>



<li>Full coverage of access to broadband networks</li>



<li>Improvement of the Environment<br>a. Water consumption per unit of GDP: down 23%<br>b. Energy consumption per unit of GDP: down 15%<br>c. Carbon dioxide emissions down 18%</li>



<li>Life all rural residents falling below the current poverty line out of poverty</li>



<li>New urban jobs more than 50 million</li>
</ol>



<p>In terms of international responsibilities, China looks at increasing its assistance to developing countries in the areas of education, medicines, disaster relief, animal protection and poverty alleviation. China will also look at safeguarding international public security and oppose any forms of terrorism.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>                                                  (Source: Report of the Work of the Government, Premier Li Keqiang, China.org.cn)</code></pre>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="550" height="359" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news21.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1767" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news21.jpg 550w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news21-300x196.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 550px) 100vw, 550px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em><em>Chinese Premier Li Keqiang delivers the government work report to nearly 3,000 legislators in the Great Hall of the People (Source: china.org.cn)</em></em></figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/01/fourth-session-of-chinas-12th-national-peoples-congress-npc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Pacific Tourism 2013 China Roadshow</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/30/south-pacific-tourism-2013-china-roadshow/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/30/south-pacific-tourism-2013-china-roadshow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[At the conclusion of the China International Travel Mart 2013 (CITM) in Kunming, a group of Pacific Tourism officials took the long trip to Beijing to partake in the South Pacific Tourism 2013 China Roadshow first stop on the 29th October 2013. The program was co-organized by the SPTO and the Pacific Trade and Invest &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/30/south-pacific-tourism-2013-china-roadshow/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">South Pacific Tourism 2013 China Roadshow</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>At the conclusion of the China International Travel Mart 2013 (CITM) in Kunming, a group of Pacific Tourism officials took the long trip to Beijing to partake in the South Pacific Tourism 2013 China Roadshow first stop on the 29th October 2013. The program was co-organized by the SPTO and the Pacific Trade and Invest office (PT&amp;I) in Beijing.</p>



<p>The Roadshow is one of many collective efforts by the region to further promote the Pacific as an attractive tourist destination to the Chinese market. Chinese travel and tourism marketing agents, journalists and other stakeholders were specifically invited by the organizers to participate in the one day event. Representing the Pacific were the SPTO and PT&amp;I, and also representatives from Vanuatu, Samoa, Fiji and Tonga.</p>



<p>The seminar kick starts with a Pacific entertainment provided by a Samoan dance group made up of Samoan students studying in Beijing, and then followed by the official launching of the Chinese Language South Pacific specialist book. Representatives from SPTO, Vanuatu and Samoa were then invited to make presentations, before the guests were openly encouraged to approach each participating country stations for a B2B session.</p>



<p>The Roadshow’s next stop was Shanghai.</p>



<p>Samoa were represented at the seminar in Beijing by Dwayne Bently – STA Marketing Manager, Mosie Su’a – Samoa Scenic Manager, Jerry Ma – Travel Link Marketing and Louis Ofele of the Samoa Embassy in Beijing.</p>



<figure class="is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-1 wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="640" height="360" data-id="1745"  src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news10.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1745" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news10.jpg 640w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news10-300x169.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="640" height="480" data-id="1746"  src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news11.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1746" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news11.jpg 640w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news11-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="640" height="480" data-id="1747"  src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news13.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1747" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news13.jpg 640w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news13-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></figure>
</figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/30/south-pacific-tourism-2013-china-roadshow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7th Seminar of Senior Defense Officials from the South Pacific</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[China held a three weeks defense seminar for senior military and police officers from 15 South Pacific and Caribbean countries hosted by the National Defense University in Beijing. It’s the 7th time that China has successfully organized the program for senior officials from the two regions. Assistant Police Commissioner Mr. Misa Talaimanu Keti represented Samoa &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">7th Seminar of Senior Defense Officials from the South Pacific</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>China held a three weeks defense seminar for senior military and police officers from 15 South Pacific and Caribbean countries hosted by the National Defense University in Beijing. It’s the 7th time that China has successfully organized the program for senior officials from the two regions.</p>



<p>Assistant Police Commissioner Mr. Misa Talaimanu Keti represented Samoa at the seminar.</p>



<p>During their 3 weeks in China, the group also visited Shanghai and Hangzhou and visited some of the military and police academies and campuses in those cities. The program has enabled senior police and military officials from the Pacific and Carribean to learn about China, but also to establish closer ties and share experiences with their Chinese counterparts on a number of security related issues including maritime surveillance and border control.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="640" height="425" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news23.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1776" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news23.jpg 640w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news23-300x199.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Photo caption: H.E. Mr. Tapusalaia Toomata (Ambassador), Mr. Misa Talaimanu Keti (Police Commissioner) and Mr. Louis Ofele (First Secretary)</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Press Statement</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/28/press-statement/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/28/press-statement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1779</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Secretary General Tuiloma Neroni Slade and Chinese Special Envoy to the China-Pacific Islands Forum dialogue， Ambassador Li Qiangmin officially launch the Pacific Islands Trade &#38; Invest office in Beijing, China The rebranding of the Pacific Islands Trade and Invest (PT&#38;I) Office in Beijing was officially launches earlier this week by Tuiloma Neroni Slade, the Secretary &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/28/press-statement/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Press Statement</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Secretary General Tuiloma Neroni Slade and Chinese Special Envoy to the China-Pacific Islands Forum dialogue， Ambassador Li Qiangmin officially launch the Pacific Islands Trade &amp; Invest office in Beijing, China</p>



<p>The rebranding of the Pacific Islands Trade and Invest (PT&amp;I) Office in Beijing was officially launches earlier this week by Tuiloma Neroni Slade, the Secretary General of the Pacific Islands Forum.</p>



<p>Under the new brand, the PT&amp;I Office in Beijing joins the network of Offices that the Pacific Islands Forum Secretariat has in Auckland, Sydney and Tokyo, including a desk in Geneva, to promote trade, investment and tourism to the benefit of the Pacific islands.</p>



<p>“Our initiative to rebrand the Beijing Office to align it with the full Pacific Islands Trade &amp; Invest network of offices will assist in ensuring that the common services available throughout these offices are also available to the clients and customers of the Beijing Office. It will allow the other offices to also benefit from the work that the Beijing Office is doing,” Mr Slade stated during the launch of rebranding. “This rebranding will assist in increasing the visibility of the work that the PT&amp;I network of offices is doing for the Pacific islands businesses,” Mr Slade added.</p>



<p>H.E. Ambassador Li Qiangmin, China’s Special Envoy to the Pacific Islands Forum Dialogue represented the Government of the People’s Republic of China at the launch.</p>



<p>“China and the Pacific enjoy strong economic complemetarities and broad prospects for cooperation with China’s advantage in capital, technology and markets and the Pacific Island Countries’ abundant resources in tourism, agriculture, fisheries and minerals,” Ambassador Li stated. “China always tries its best to make concrete contributions to the economic and social development of PICs,” Ambassador Li added.</p>



<p>“The Forum Trade Office has made unremitting efforts to facilitate exchanges and cooperation in such fields as trade, investment and tourism between China and PICs, and plays an important role in deepening our mutual understanding and promoting mutual benefit,” Ambassador Li said.</p>



<p>A rejuvenated website in Chinese language is part of the rebranded PT&amp;I Beijing Office. The website contains in formation about the Pacific Islands on trade, tourism and investment opportunities and focuses on the needs of the Chinese speaking clinets.</p>



<p>Pacific Island Ambassadors in Beijing, and Private Sector representatives working with the businesses in the Pacific were among the guests who attended the launch at the Great Wall Sheraton Hotel in Beijing.</p>



<p>“I want to thank the People’s Republic of China for its continued support and commitment to the Pacific Islands Forum and to the countries of our region through its substantive programme of development assistance, including people-to-people exchanges. These contribute substantially to the advancement of capacities of Pacific governments, private sector and the communities at large primarily in the areas of infrastructure, health, education, agriculture, tourism and fisheries,” Mr Slade said.</p>



<p>The Secretary General was on an official visit to Beijing, at the invitation of the Government of the People’s Republic of China. the Secretary General met with State Councilor H.E. Yang Jiechi and the Minister of Foreign Affairs, H.E. Wang Yi, and other Ministers and high ranking Official during his visit.<br>(Ends)</p>



<p>For meida enquiries, please contact Ms Ateca Tora, the Forum Secretariat’s Information Management Coordinator on phone: (+679) 331 2600 or email: atecat@forumsec.org,fj</p>



<p>Source: Pacific Islands Trade &amp; Invest office in Beijing</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="768" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news25.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1780" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news25.jpg 1024w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news25-300x225.jpg 300w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news25-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">From left to right : Trade Commissioner Mr. Sam Savou (Pacific Islands Trade &amp; Invest) , H.E. Mr. Christopher Mero (Papua New Guinea), Secretary General Mr. Tuiloma Neroni Slade (Pacific Islands Forum Secretariat), H.E. Tapusalaia Terry Toomata (Samoa), H.E. Mr Siamelie Latu (Tonga), Chargé d&#8217;affaires a.i. Mr Carl Apis (Federated States of Micronesia).</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/28/press-statement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
