<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Samoa Embassy</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/SE_Github_Site/index.php/category/uncategorized/feed/?simply_static_page=4978" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy</link>
	<description>Beijing</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 02:31:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 05:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[8th September 2017, Sheraton Aggie Grey’s Hotel, Apia-Samoa Pacific Leaders gathered in Samoa in September to attend the annual Pacific Islands Forum. The Agenda for this year’s meeting included the Small Islands &#160;Developing States Leaders Meeting, the Pacific ACP Leaders Meeting, the Official Opening of the 48th Pacific Islands Forum, the Forum Leaders Dialogue with &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>8th September 2017, Sheraton Aggie Grey’s Hotel, Apia-Samoa</p>



<p>Pacific Leaders gathered in Samoa in September to attend the annual Pacific Islands Forum. The Agenda for this year’s meeting included the Small Islands &nbsp;Developing States Leaders Meeting, the Pacific ACP Leaders Meeting, the Official Opening of the 48th Pacific Islands Forum, the Forum Leaders Dialogue with Civil Society Organizations and Private Sector, the 48th PIF Plenary Sessions with Associate Member and Forum Observers and Post Forum Dialogue Partners and the Forum Leaders Retreat.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Also during the meeting week, The Pacific Islands Trade and Investment Commission in China, the Samoa Embassy in China and its Chinese partners hosted a Seminar for business leaders, Officials and others interested in building economic links between China and the Pacific. The aim of the Seminar was to learn about the opportunities and challenges through participation in industry-focused panel discussions on trade, investment and tourism.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The opening statement for the Seminar was delivered by Samoa’s Minister of Commerce, Industry and Labour, Hon. Lautafi Selafi Purcell. Presentations on related topics were delivered by H.E Mr Du Qiwen China’s Special Envoy for the China Pacific Islands Forum Dialogue, Mr. Shiu Raj Director Policy &amp; Economic Governance, Pacific Islands Forum Secretariat, Mr. Yin Zonghua Vice President China Council for the Promotion of International Trade (CCPIT), and Mr. Guo Wanda Executive Vice President China Development Institute (CDI).</p>



<p>The one day event was attended by members of Samoa’s private sector, Government Officials, Pacific delegates and delegates from China. The Seminar focused on three main areas for panel discussions;</p>



<p>1.Chinese Partnerships in Pacific Infrastructure and Connectivity</p>



<p>2.Sustainable Tourism Development</p>



<p>3.Value-adding to Pacific Fisheries</p>



<p>The Seminar proved to be a great opportunity for the exchange of ideas and discussion of opportunities to further strengthen trade, investment and tourism between China and the Pacific.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="javascript:;"><img decoding="async" src="http://www.samoaembassy.cn/UploadFiles/2017-10/2/2017102401.jpg" alt="The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development"/></a></figure>



<p>Opening Statement: Hon. Lautafi Selafi Purcell, Minister of Commerce, Industry and Labour, Samoa.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="javascript:;"><img decoding="async" src="http://www.samoaembassy.cn/UploadFiles/2017-10/2/2017102402.jpg" alt="The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development"/></a></figure>



<p>China and the Pacific Islands: H.E Mr Du Qiwen, China’s Special Envoy for the China Pacific Islands Forum Dialogue.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/07/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China International Travel Mart, 11-13 November 2016</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/06/china-international-travel-mart-11-13-november-2016/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The CITM (China International Travel Mart) is well known as the largest International Travel Mart in Asia which has attracted audiences from across the globe.&#160; The annual event is alternated between Shanghai and Kunming with this years’ event being held in Shanghai. The CITM is an event jointly hosted by the China National Tourism Administration, &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/06/china-international-travel-mart-11-13-november-2016/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">China International Travel Mart, 11-13 November 2016</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The CITM (China International Travel Mart) is well known as the largest International Travel Mart in Asia which has attracted audiences from across the globe.&nbsp; The annual event is alternated between Shanghai and Kunming with this years’ event being held in Shanghai.<br><br>The CITM is an event jointly hosted by the China National Tourism Administration, the Civil Aviation Administration of China, and the Shanghai Municipals People’s Government.<br>The event was launched with the Official Opening Ceremony lead by the CNTA Chairman Mr. Li Jinzao with this year’s guest of honor Minister of Tourism and Sports for Thailand, H.E Kobkarn Wattanavrangkul.</p>



<p>Samoa’s delegation to the CITM 2016 included the Minister for Tourism, Hon. Sala Fata Pinati and his good lady Mrs. Cecilia Pinati, the Ambassador of Samoa to China, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, the CEO of the Samoa Tourism Authority, Mrs. Papalii Sonja Hunter, Marketing Manager, Mr. Dwayne Bentley, and First Secretary Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.</p>



<p>Other Pacific Islands that were also present at this years’ event included, Fiji, FSM, Tahiti, PNG, and Vanuatu.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="573" height="341" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news3.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1738" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news3.jpg 573w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news3-300x179.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 573px) 100vw, 573px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Lunch Meeting hosted by the Vice Chairman of the China National Tourism Authority, Mr. Du Jiang.</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="571" height="428" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news4.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1739" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news4.jpg 571w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news4-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 571px) 100vw, 571px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">The Hon. Minister for Tourism, Sala Fata Pinati, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, CEO of STA Papalii Sonja Hunter and First Secretary, Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="575" height="430" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news5.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1740" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news5.jpg 575w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news5-300x224.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 575px) 100vw, 575px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Pacific Delegates at the Expo Arena</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="573" height="429" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news6.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1741" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news6.jpg 573w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news6-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 573px) 100vw, 573px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Pacific Delegates at the Opening Cocktail</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guangzhou Tourism Expo, 9-11 September 2016</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/05/guangzhou-tourism-expo-9-11-september-2016/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1630</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Samoa in association with PITI attended the Guangzhou International Tourism Fair this year along aside other Pacific Island Countries such as PNG and FSM. The 3 day event was held at the well known Canton Fair Complex from the 9th- 11th September 2016. The Expo housed nine theme pavilions and 4,500 standard booths. Present at &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/05/guangzhou-tourism-expo-9-11-september-2016/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Guangzhou Tourism Expo, 9-11 September 2016</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Samoa in association with PITI attended the Guangzhou International Tourism Fair this year along aside other Pacific Island Countries such as PNG and FSM.</p>



<p>The 3 day event was held at the well known Canton Fair Complex from the 9th- 11th September 2016. The Expo housed nine theme pavilions and 4,500 standard booths. Present at this years Fair were 55 countries and more than 3,000 exhibitors. Also present during this years’ Fair were some special guests which included five Parliamentarians from Samoa, Hon. Tofa Foleni Loi, Hon. Salausa Dr. John Ah Ching, Hon. Leaana Ronnie Posini, Hon. Afoa Amituanai Mauli, and Hon. Fuimaono Teo. Further, The Governor and Vice Governor of Guangdong Province also visited the Pacific Booth and had brief discussions with Ambassador Tapusalaia on Tourism cooperation between China and Samoa.</p>



<p>The event also featured a tourism exhibition, a tourism hypermarket, a hospitality supplies fair, seminars, conferences, competitions, signing ceremonies and other events.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="571" height="424" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news7.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1742" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news7.jpg 571w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news7-300x223.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 571px) 100vw, 571px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Ambassador Tapusalaia meets with Governor of Guangdong Province, Mr. Zhu Xiaodan.</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="426" height="570" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1736" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news1.jpg 426w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news1-224x300.jpg 224w" sizes="(max-width: 426px) 100vw, 426px" /></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="573" height="533" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news2.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1737" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news2.jpg 573w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news2-300x279.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 573px) 100vw, 573px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Samoa Embassy with Parliamentarians from Samoa.</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First World Conference on Tourism for Development</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/04/first-world-conference-on-tourism-for-development/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 08:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1759</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[18-21 May 2016 The First World Conference on Tourism for Development was held in Beijing from the 18-21 May 2016. Samoa’s delegation to the meeting was led by the Minister for Tourism Hon. Selafi Joseph Purcell with a delegation comprising of the Ambassador of Samoa to China, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, the CEO of Samoa &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/04/first-world-conference-on-tourism-for-development/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">First World Conference on Tourism for Development</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>18-21 May 2016</p>



<p>The First World Conference on Tourism for Development was held in Beijing from the 18-21 May 2016. Samoa’s delegation to the meeting was led by the Minister for Tourism Hon. Selafi Joseph Purcell with a delegation comprising of the Ambassador of Samoa to China, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, the CEO of Samoa Tourism Authority (STA) Ms. Papalii Sonja Hunter, Counselor of the Embassy of Samoa Ms. Helen Chou-Lee Tanuvasa and the First Secretary, Ms. Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.<br>The event was jointly organized by the Government of China and the World Tourism Organization (UNWTO) to encourage deliberations and create a better understanding of tourism’s contribution to development including poverty alleviation and peace. Further, China as the Chair of G20 also hosted the 7th G20 Tourism Minister’s Meeting during the event. Several heads of states as well as tourism ministers and senior officials from over 100 countries participated.</p>



<p>The UN has declared 2017 as the International Year of Sustainable Tourism for Development and a unique opportunity to portray tourism’s potential to help transform the world into a place of prosperity and wellbeing for all mankind. The conference highlighted the fast growing socio-economic benefits resulting from tourism and how tourism can stimulate economic growth, create employment opportunities and help small communities out of poverty.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="389" height="290" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news16.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1750" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news16.jpg 389w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news16-300x224.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 389px) 100vw, 389px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: From the left, Hon. Minister for Tourism of Tonga, Hon. Minister for Tourism of Samoa, Chairman of the China National Tourism Administration, Hon. Minister for Tourism of PNG, Hon Deputy Prime Minister and Minister for Tourism of Vanuatu)</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="388" height="288" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news17.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1751" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news17.jpg 388w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news17-300x223.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 388px) 100vw, 388px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: Chairman of the China National Tourism Administration, Mr Li Jinzao together with the Minister for Tourism of Samoa Hon. Lautafi Joseph Purcell)</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="207" height="275" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news19.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1752"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: Minister for Tourism of Samoa Hon. Lautafi Joseph Purcell and CEO of the Samoa Tourism Authority, Mrs. Papalii Sonja Hunter together with a performer from Guizhou Province)</figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="355" height="267" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news20.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1760" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news20.jpg 355w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news20-300x226.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 355px) 100vw, 355px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Photo: Minister for Tourism of Samoa Hon. Lautafi Joseph Purcell with the Ambassador of Samoa in Beijing, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata)</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 17th China International Vegetable Sci-Tech Fair</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 08:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1762</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[19th-21st April 2016 The Embassy of Samoa was invited to participate in this year’s China International Vegetable Fair which was held in Shouguang City, Shandong Province. The China International Vegetable Fair is the largest and most popular industrial exhibition meeting in China for the agriculture sector. The theme for this year’s event was ‘Green science &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The 17th China International Vegetable Sci-Tech Fair</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>19th-21st April 2016</em></p>



<p>The Embassy of Samoa was invited to participate in this year’s China International Vegetable Fair which was held in Shouguang City, Shandong Province.</p>



<p>The China International Vegetable Fair is the largest and most popular industrial exhibition meeting in China for the agriculture sector. The theme for this year’s event was ‘Green science technology and future under the principle of science, feature, innovation and practice for international agricultural exchange’.</p>



<p>The opening ceremony was attended by government officials, diplomats and hundreds of local farmers and members of the local business community. The ceremony was followed by an exhibition fair which occupied 450 thousand square meters of land including 11 exhibition halls, a foreign products exhibition pavilion, a vegetable museum, a vegetable picking park, numerous outdoor booths and 12 branches of exhibition company locations. Shouguang City is well known as China’s ‘Home of Vegetables’ and this year’s conference highlighted and showcased the extensive growth in produce and innovation of the agriculture sector in China.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="321" height="236" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news14.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1748" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news14.jpg 321w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news14-300x221.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 321px) 100vw, 321px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>(Photo: Far Right, Ambassador of Samoa H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata at the Opening Ceremony)</em></figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="171" height="230" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/news15.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1749"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>(Photo: Tomato: One of the most popular fruits displayed at the Fair)</em></figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/12/03/the-17th-china-international-vegetable-sci-tech-fair/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7th Seminar of Senior Defense Officials from the South Pacific</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/?p=1775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[China held a three weeks defense seminar for senior military and police officers from 15 South Pacific and Caribbean countries hosted by the National Defense University in Beijing. It’s the 7th time that China has successfully organized the program for senior officials from the two regions. Assistant Police Commissioner Mr. Misa Talaimanu Keti represented Samoa &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">7th Seminar of Senior Defense Officials from the South Pacific</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>China held a three weeks defense seminar for senior military and police officers from 15 South Pacific and Caribbean countries hosted by the National Defense University in Beijing. It’s the 7th time that China has successfully organized the program for senior officials from the two regions.</p>



<p>Assistant Police Commissioner Mr. Misa Talaimanu Keti represented Samoa at the seminar.</p>



<p>During their 3 weeks in China, the group also visited Shanghai and Hangzhou and visited some of the military and police academies and campuses in those cities. The program has enabled senior police and military officials from the Pacific and Carribean to learn about China, but also to establish closer ties and share experiences with their Chinese counterparts on a number of security related issues including maritime surveillance and border control.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="640" height="425" src="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news23.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1776" srcset="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news23.jpg 640w, https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/news23-300x199.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Photo caption: H.E. Mr. Tapusalaia Toomata (Ambassador), Mr. Misa Talaimanu Keti (Police Commissioner) and Mr. Louis Ofele (First Secretary)</figcaption></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/29/7th-seminar-of-senior-defense-officials-from-the-south-pacific/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
