<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>samoanembassy &#8211; Samoa Embassy</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/SE_Github_Site/index.php/author/samoanembassy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy</link>
	<description>Beijing</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 14:09:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Guangzhou Tourism Expo, 9-11 September 2016</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/27/guangzhou-tourism-expo-9-11-september-2016/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 14:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1630</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Samoa in association with PITI attended the Guangzhou International Tourism Fair this year along aside other Pacific Island Countries such as PNG and FSM. The 3 day event was held at the well known Canton Fair Complex from the 9th- 11th September 2016. The Expo housed nine theme pavilions and 4,500 standard booths. Present at &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/27/guangzhou-tourism-expo-9-11-september-2016/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Guangzhou Tourism Expo, 9-11 September 2016</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Samoa in association with PITI attended the Guangzhou International Tourism Fair this year along aside other Pacific Island Countries such as PNG and FSM.</p>



<p>The 3 day event was held at the well known Canton Fair Complex from the 9th- 11th September 2016. The Expo housed nine theme pavilions and 4,500 standard booths. Present at this years Fair were 55 countries and more than 3,000 exhibitors. Also present during this years’ Fair were some special guests which included five Parliamentarians from Samoa, Hon. Tofa Foleni Loi, Hon. Salausa Dr. John Ah Ching, Hon. Leaana Ronnie Posini, Hon. Afoa Amituanai Mauli, and Hon. Fuimaono Teo. Further, The Governor and Vice Governor of Guangdong Province also visited the Pacific Booth and had brief discussions with Ambassador Tapusalaia on Tourism cooperation between China and Samoa.</p>



<p>The event also featured a tourism exhibition, a tourism hypermarket, a hospitality supplies fair, seminars, conferences, competitions, signing ceremonies and other events.</p>



<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<a href="javascript:;"></a><br>Ambassador Tapusalaia meets with Governor of Guangdong Province, Mr. Zhu Xiaodan.<br><a href="javascript:;"></a><br><br><br><a href="javascript:;"></a><br>Samoa Embassy with Parliamentarians from Samoa.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China International Travel Mart, 11-13 November 2016</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/27/china-international-travel-mart-11-13-november-2016/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 14:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1623</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The CITM (China International Travel Mart) is well known as the largest International Travel Mart in Asia which has attracted audiences from across the globe.&#160; The annual event is alternated between Shanghai and Kunming with this years’ event being held in Shanghai. The CITM is an event jointly hosted by the China National Tourism Administration, &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/27/china-international-travel-mart-11-13-november-2016/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">China International Travel Mart, 11-13 November 2016</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The CITM (China International Travel Mart) is well known as the largest International Travel Mart in Asia which has attracted audiences from across the globe.&nbsp; The annual event is alternated between Shanghai and Kunming with this years’ event being held in Shanghai.<br><br>The CITM is an event jointly hosted by the China National Tourism Administration, the Civil Aviation Administration of China, and the Shanghai Municipals People’s Government.<br>The event was launched with the Official Opening Ceremony lead by the CNTA Chairman Mr. Li Jinzao with this year’s guest of honor Minister of Tourism and Sports for Thailand, H.E Kobkarn Wattanavrangkul.</p>



<p>Samoa’s delegation to the CITM 2016 included the Minister for Tourism, Hon. Sala Fata Pinati and his good lady Mrs. Cecilia Pinati, the Ambassador of Samoa to China, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, the CEO of the Samoa Tourism Authority, Mrs. Papalii Sonja Hunter, Marketing Manager, Mr. Dwayne Bentley, and First Secretary Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.</p>



<p>Other Pacific Islands that were also present at this years’ event included, Fiji, FSM, Tahiti, PNG, and Vanuatu.<br><br><a href="javascript:;"></a><br>Lunch Meeting hosted by the Vice Chairman of the China National Tourism Authority, Mr. Du Jiang.<br><br><br><a href="javascript:;"></a><br>The Hon. Minister for Tourism, Sala Fata Pinati, H.E Tapusalaia Terry Toomata, CEO of STA Papalii Sonja Hunter and First Secretary, Dorothy Ah Ching Meredith.<br><br><br><a href="javascript:;"></a><br>Pacific Delegates at the Expo Arena<br><br><br><a href="javascript:;"></a><br>Pacific Delegates at the Opening Cocktail</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development</title>
		<link>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/24/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/24/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[samoanembassy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 05:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:8888/Samoa%20Embassy/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[8th September 2017, Sheraton Aggie Grey’s Hotel, Apia-Samoa Pacific Leaders gathered in Samoa in September to attend the annual Pacific Islands Forum. The Agenda for this year’s meeting included the Small Islands &#160;Developing States Leaders Meeting, the Pacific ACP Leaders Meeting, the Official Opening of the 48th Pacific Islands Forum, the Forum Leaders Dialogue with &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/24/hello-world/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>8th September 2017, Sheraton Aggie Grey’s Hotel, Apia-Samoa</p>



<p>Pacific Leaders gathered in Samoa in September to attend the annual Pacific Islands Forum. The Agenda for this year’s meeting included the Small Islands &nbsp;Developing States Leaders Meeting, the Pacific ACP Leaders Meeting, the Official Opening of the 48th Pacific Islands Forum, the Forum Leaders Dialogue with Civil Society Organizations and Private Sector, the 48th PIF Plenary Sessions with Associate Member and Forum Observers and Post Forum Dialogue Partners and the Forum Leaders Retreat.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Also during the meeting week, The Pacific Islands Trade and Investment Commission in China, the Samoa Embassy in China and its Chinese partners hosted a Seminar for business leaders, Officials and others interested in building economic links between China and the Pacific. The aim of the Seminar was to learn about the opportunities and challenges through participation in industry-focused panel discussions on trade, investment and tourism.&nbsp;</p>



<p>The opening statement for the Seminar was delivered by Samoa’s Minister of Commerce, Industry and Labour, Hon. Lautafi Selafi Purcell. Presentations on related topics were delivered by H.E Mr Du Qiwen China’s Special Envoy for the China Pacific Islands Forum Dialogue, Mr. Shiu Raj Director Policy &amp; Economic Governance, Pacific Islands Forum Secretariat, Mr. Yin Zonghua Vice President China Council for the Promotion of International Trade (CCPIT), and Mr. Guo Wanda Executive Vice President China Development Institute (CDI).</p>



<p>The one day event was attended by members of Samoa’s private sector, Government Officials, Pacific delegates and delegates from China. The Seminar focused on three main areas for panel discussions;</p>



<p>1.Chinese Partnerships in Pacific Infrastructure and Connectivity</p>



<p>2.Sustainable Tourism Development</p>



<p>3.Value-adding to Pacific Fisheries</p>



<p>The Seminar proved to be a great opportunity for the exchange of ideas and discussion of opportunities to further strengthen trade, investment and tourism between China and the Pacific.&nbsp;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="javascript:;"><img decoding="async" src="http://www.samoaembassy.cn/UploadFiles/2017-10/2/2017102401.jpg" alt="The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development"/></a></figure>



<p>Opening Statement: Hon. Lautafi Selafi Purcell, Minister of Commerce, Industry and Labour, Samoa.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><a href="javascript:;"><img decoding="async" src="http://www.samoaembassy.cn/UploadFiles/2017-10/2/2017102402.jpg" alt="The 21st Century Maritime Silk Road: Pacific Islands-China Economic Cooperation for Sustainable Development"/></a></figure>



<p>China and the Pacific Islands: H.E Mr Du Qiwen, China’s Special Envoy for the China Pacific Islands Forum Dialogue.</p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://pos-dev.github.io/samoa-embassy/index.php/2022/11/24/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
